<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="documents">
  <title>Documents</title>
  <taskbody>
    <context>
      <p>
        A document is generated from an associated schema. They are generally used as inputs into deployments such as the sed, the netsim information etc.
        These documents make use of the <xref type="concept" href="../enmSedAutoPopulation.xml">autopopulation</xref> feature to populate all of the keys that it obtains from the associated schema.
      </p>
      <p><b>Objective</b></p>
      <p>Create a new document for the Deployment Inventory Tool</p>
      <p>
        <b>Outline</b>
        <ol>
          <li><xref href="#openDocument">Open the Document View</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#createDocument">Create New Document</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#enterDetails">Enter the Document Details</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#saveDocument">Save Document</xref></li>
        </ol>
      </p>
    </context>
    <prereq>
      <p>To create a new document the user must have the following:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Associated Schema already created in the tool</li>
      </ul>
    </prereq>
    <steps>
      <step id="openDocument">
        <cmd>Open the Document View</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the document view from the nav bar at the top</p>
          <p>Select document type from dropdown (SED, Managed Config or Other)</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="createDocument">
        <cmd>Create New Document</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the <b>Create new document</b> button</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="enterDetails">
        <cmd>Enter the Document Details</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Enter the details as shown below.</p>
          <p><b>NOTE:</b> Restrictions on the fields are as follows: </p>
          <ul>
            <li><b>Name</b> must be between 5 and 80 characters</li>
            <li><b>Show Snapshots</b> option may be turned on if you want snapshot versions of schemas to be visible in the next step</li>
            <li><b>Schema</b> must be an existing schema</li>
            <li>Based on schema chosen you will need to fill out the document as needed.</li>
            <li><b>Auto Populate</b> option for SEDs may be turned on and off. When fields are autopopulated they are removed from the UI, \n
             more info can be found <xref type="concept" href="../enmSedAutoPopulation.xml">here</xref>.</li>
            <li>If you have an existing document you wish to paste in the <b>Paste Mode</b> can be toggled.</li>
            <li><b><xref type="concept" href="../managedConfigs.xml">Managed Configs</xref></b> can be attached using the + symbol.</li>
          </ul>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="saveDocument">
        <cmd>Save Document</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the <b>Save</b> button and you will be redirected back to the previous page</p>
          <p><b>NOTE:</b> Document will not save if any fields are invalid (RED in UI)</p>
        </info>
      </step>
    </steps>
    <result>
      <p>A New Document is created in the Deployment Inventory Tool.</p>
    </result>
  </taskbody>
</task>
