<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<task id="projects">
  <title>Projects</title>
  <taskbody>
    <context>
      <p>
        A project within the Deployment Inventory Tool is intended to be a representation of
        a project within the associated cloud pod.
      </p>
      <p><b>Objective</b></p>
      <p>Create a new project for the Deployment Inventory Tool</p>
      <p>
        <b>Outline</b>
        <ol>
          <li><xref href="#openProject">Open the Project View</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#createProject">Create New Project</xref>  </li>
          <li><xref href="#enterDetails">Enter the Project Details</xref></li>
          <li><xref href="#saveProject">Save Project</xref></li>
        </ol>
      </p>
    </context>
    <prereq>
      <p>To create a new project the user must have the following:</p>
      <ul>
        <li>Associated Pod already created in the tool</li>
      </ul>
    </prereq>
    <steps>
      <step id="openProject">
        <cmd>Open the Project View</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the project view from the nav bar at the top</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="createProject">
        <cmd>Create New Project</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Click the <b>Create new project</b> button as shown below</p>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="enterDetails">
        <cmd>Enter the Project Details</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>Enter the details as shown below.</p>
          <p><b>NOTE:</b> Restrictions on the fields are as follows: </p>
          <ul>
            <li>All fields are required</li>
            <li><b>Name</b> must be unique within pod and unique when paired with Openstack Project Id</li>
            <li><b>Pod</b> must be an existing pod that the user has created</li>
            <li><b>Network</b> at least one valid network is needed and must not overlap with network for another project</li>
            <li><b>IPv4 and IPv6 Start</b> must be a valid address</li>
            <li><b>IPv4 and IPv6 End</b> must be a valid address</li>
            </ul>
        </info>
      </step>
      <step id="saveProject">
        <cmd>Save Project</cmd>
        <info>
          <p>
            Click the <b>Save</b> button and you will be redirected back to the previous page
            where you can see the newly created project as well as the pod it resides in
            with new options to edit and delete that project.
          </p>
          <p><b>NOTE:</b> Project will not save if any fields are invalid (RED in UI)</p>
        </info>
      </step>
    </steps>
    <result>
      <p>A New Project is created in the Deployment Inventory Tool.</p>
    </result>
  </taskbody>
</task>
